We have so much stuff to carry around these days – mobile phones, keys, credit cards and laptops.
如今我们有太多东西要随身携带——手机、钥匙、信用卡和笔记本电脑。
Some of us might stuff them into various pockets in our clothes and others will put them in a bag.
我们中的一些人可能会把它们塞进衣服的各个口袋里，而另一些人则会把它们放在包里。
For women this might be a practical and trendy handbag.
对女性来说，这可能是一个实用又时髦的（trendy）手提包。
But how are men supposed to carry things around and look cool?
但男性要怎么携带东西又看起来很酷呢？
The answer is a manbag!
答案是男士包！
They are the height of fashion at the moment – a stylish accessory that modern men are carrying around.
它们目前是最流行的——一种现代男性随身携带的时尚配饰。
I'm a little cynical about these must-have items – let's face it, a manbag by any other name is a bag and I have one - my trusty backpack.
我对这些必备品有点愤世嫉俗（cynical）——面对现实吧，不管叫什么，男士包就是个包，而且我就有一个——我可靠的双肩背包。
However, senior fashion analyst for market research company Mintel, Tamara Senders, describes a manbag as "a bag worn by men, including backpacks and other styles such as shoulder bags."
然而，市场研究公司英敏特（Mintel）的高级时尚分析师塔玛拉・森德斯（Tamara Senders）将男士包描述为“男性背的包，包括背包以及其他款式，如肩包”。
I can't see my old backpack being a style icon, but maybe I'm just not on-trend: According to Mintel, 15 per cent of men bought one in the UK last year.
我不觉得我的旧背包会成为时尚标志，但也许我只是跟不上潮流：据英敏特的数据，去年在英国，15%的男性购买了男士包。
Maybe it's the name that's putting me off.
也许是这个名字让我反感。
Why does a bag have to have a gender?
为什么包还要分性别呢？
I suppose they're being marketed as a stylish fashion item designed to look good on men.
我想它们正在被当作专为男性设计、看起来很有型的时尚单品来推销。
I've heard that many big names have flocked to adopt the trend.
我听说很多名人都热衷于追随这一潮流。
Pharrell Williams, David Beckham and Kanye West, are just some of those who've been spotted rocking a manbag.
法瑞尔・威廉姆斯（Pharrell Williams）、大卫・贝克汉姆（David Beckham）和坎耶・维斯特（Kanye West），只是被看到背男士包名人中的一部分。
My reservations about being seen carrying one may be down to my Britishness.
我对被人看到背着男士包有所顾虑，这可能归因于我是英国人。
According to Nick Carvell, the Contributing Fashion Editor for GQ magazine: "In Britain we are still very tied up with that idea of masculinity that is almost so fragile that it can be dented by carrying a bag."
据《GQ》杂志特约时尚编辑尼克・卡维尔（Nick Carvell）说：“在英国，我们仍然非常纠结于那种男子气概的观念，这种观念几乎如此脆弱，以至于背个包都能被削弱。”
So, while some British men might think a manbag to be effeminate and not very 'macho', he thinks that many Europeans don't have an issue with toting such a fashionable item.
所以，虽然一些英国男性可能认为男士包娘娘腔（effeminate），不太有“男子气概”（macho），但他认为很多欧洲人对携带（toting）这样一个时尚单品并不在意。
Of course, if I was to exchange my old backpack for a manbag, it would come at a price.
当然，如果我要用旧背包换一个男士包，那可得付出一定的代价（花高价）。
With people like Louis Vuitton, Fendi, Gucci and Dolce and Gabbana designing these bags, they can come with a hefty price tag.
像路易威登（Louis Vuitton）、芬迪（Fendi）、古驰（Gucci）和杜嘉班纳（Dolce and Gabbana）这些品牌所设计出来的包，价格可能会很高昂（hefty）。
I suppose that's the price of fashion!
我想这就是时尚的代价！
And apparently, if I had any spare cash, I could complete my designer outfit by buying a murse – that's a man's purse!
而且显然，如果我有闲钱，我可以买一个murse来搭配我的设计师潮服——也就是男士用的钱包！
I suppose fashions change and we have come a long way from the days when men carried their things in a very masculine briefcase - sturdy, sensible and practical.
我想时尚在变化，男性用非常有男子气概，结实、朴素又实用的公文包来装东西的那个时代已经过去了很久。
Now, it seems, we have to put as much thought into buying a bag as we do into buying our clothes.
现在，似乎我们在买包时要像买衣服一样深思熟虑。